I paid the bill online. It is important
that I buy school stuff for my kids, I
order movies online, and I order groceries online,
and even more so for health insurance
online because that is also important. You all
know how important health insurance
is, but I am also forced by habit.
Then I will ask
why health insurance is important. Health
insurance is important. As you
know that healthcare costs are increasing.
A small operation like
cataract operation costs ₹50 and it will increase further in the
coming time. There are
side effects of this in Asian countries. The
medical infection rate of India
is 14% which is quite high, so it means
that your treatment cost is also going to be
expensive, hence you
need to maintain. Secondly, by taking health insurance,
your pension responsibility towards
your help expenses gets declared
on the insurance company, so you do
not have to take any pressure of this, you can have peace of mind
and whatever that medical  In case of emergency
your health insurance company will take care of it, for this
we need a good health
insurance policy, today we will
talk about it from Amazon, through which the village
head secretary and that sensitive
we will see how you
can buy the policy through online application and
can ask the complete
process online, you can also follow today's video for
your policy, if you
eat body
you will have to download the application, the
question is no, you will download the application,
here you will select health insurance
and do that, after that
some information will come back from you
which you need to give, first of all they will
ask you for pin code, why pin code
because on the basis of your pin code it will be decided
that you have made the payment, then you will pay
more premium according to this zone, decidedly
pin code is important, then after that
you will be asked for an individual
policy, till then this marriage is broken, you should
take it from Britain, so this I have
reached around my, there in silver
Miles Sadhu easily doctor, then with you the
village these products should cover all India, you
can select the major,
super nice to you in the express  I
could have fun in the exam for some time and then I will add it
as I showed you in the question,
I abused the members page
and corrected it, as soon as I continue,
this is a very related question there
because material information is your song, the
question will be asked the first option will be
agreement happy, if there is no infection or
medical condition, now select it
and add it, now one medical condition
money life after she is that you do not smoke
but there was hospitalization, then these things are
necessary for you to make before taking the policy,
deposit is medical information,
inside it a little bit of policy of the
type fuel, then confirmation all that
you have written is smoking, so as I
checked and this mixture of Bikaner style was
automatically suggested to me, it was always the
best according to my
location and number and a
detailed review of Sania Mirza policy will be done,
it will include with sexual
areas 30, you
can deduct a punishment time for yourself as per your wish in the event show
10  Minutes less to turn off the light, so I
can always change it with me by moving it back and forth like this, so I will
take the Tubelight point, so we
click on the nine in the last year, so
diseases appointment that they are
in the minister of the party and on your birthday this cut
only one year figure was with me, then 1GB can be
chosen, so by taking the bank balance
map match, you can push it forward,
laugh, you see what the serial is
slanted, by the way I would like to tell you that this year
's details are on our channel face,
whatever superstition line can be kept here, whatever
details can be made easy, will come from this thing
and a little flame on the table,
bank account in the hospital means hundred percent of the
hospital is admitted,
after the differential oil, there is a check salary button, that is,
we are the same hospitalization office collection,
hence hospitalization
significance of notification, all the updates,
so I can get all the question related PM post after
life but I want to do this good to this party,
slaughter of other animals,
accident-free close loop test, positive
energy ventures test  It is only once a year for all those who are
above half an inch seventeen
in spinach, you get vitamin C Mahesh
points network, then if there is a network then it will come close to it, you get unlimited
online
with a leadership quality, you get free of
cost complimentary unlimited online
porn that you can say 50% less salt from
your sources, I mean, like understand
that OPT office used to do magic for you, the
office is near you, you can sit here and
convince a doctor, you
can also get online, so unlimited
transportation is available in that
side, the budget for vitamin A hospitalization, so
because of the wing, if you have a hospital
and the hospitalization takes flex, then that
introduction in the middle is the next, the best
thing is Chuteya world class hospital
question network, you have a great and that
every kuni kuni print out, if it is settled,
you have to
think, then you have access to good
hospitals, first India and animation
approval according to taste,
depression go to the hospital, 10,000
plus go to the hospital and change fold,
so moment  The approval time is
only in between, which means you get this
sewing experience and you are made an Indet
Relationship Manager. Next, the
company gives you a report if you can know your fit, then
report for copying
dresses. If you start some chat daily, then the
company gives you some less, if you do
online course of the river and
minimum police plan your means 365, when you
eat it with dal-rice, then the
company gives you five likes and if you
work more than this, then this account
increases further, so if you
take mother Hansraj turtle and work more, then
human flag discount and pregnant,
then you can get this maximum up to ten percent by
requesting the minister, so
as told, the companies are doing some boys
smooth related work, that
hospitalization messages are being carefully watched, it will
work like that, you will have a minimum balance set and
along with that you will get rewards, then you
cannot see your own, then you
can increase your reward points, if your taste increases then your
benefit will increase due to which you  If you look at your policy,
two screens will flash and you will get to know that
guys, Bigg Boss point that I am late
and how many lines do I have on my pimple, so
friends, today I am going to tell you something and for
discount, as I had
talked to you, there is address network of Tent House Dress Hospital,
so
before taking the hospital policy, you can check whether
Mansingh Hospital is available in your area,
you can search the hospital of your area by
my location and by name, even here
we can enter the location, see this is the location, if we
search by the name of the hospital, then
you will know where you
can get it and which hospital you
can go to, before taking this policy,
you should know that I have to enter my location, so if
I am searching the file location, Naina
Kajrare Party Rose Garden, Instant, then the
judgment came, I will see all the nearby hospitals, so
as if there was a hospital in my location,
carefully we will look at Lotus Hospital
Center for Sight Kapoor Medical Center Sajna
Institute Amit Nursing Home
Hospital near Garden Nursing Home and to all, so
I will click here, it will go for
measuring the land, the second one will take me there
Chanakya Niti can clarify
section Balaji Hospital most of the
colleagues realize that I am wrong then I
showed that Deepak is in the list and
similar way I searched from this location, I
want to search there,
you have to chant so this product will be
for you if you click on about then your
vacation life will be like we have already
taken more tension and
in 2010 the quotation comes, we saw
face to face debate 140, we told
how is the Congress's rule in the state, its
basic PM came, article further
gave training, to click on policy, so
quite simple micro along with
women living and in college,
black marks go, details madrasa positive, if you have
your medical history then
android value and medical history and a
policy to watch the video sometime but and
with medical, Valentine Allah's
polythene goes to this,
how to take less health care, the paper was from this, you have any
one duty, let's go here hundred
percent company's online classes
loot
if we will talk about other things, this type of
disease was daughter, this was good  The thing is that only
one can do it, if we
talk about claims settlement then
take coconut, gold chain, judgment is followed on IT cell, which is
gold, I will tell you the holes and
qualities if you
buy the policy directly through the application without
warning, idli 50% year, thanks to syrup,
50% free difference comes up, even if you are not an
MS Word quality customer, you
can buy quality quickly, so
transparent in two ways, on this occasion,
Intercity Express, it happens that intercourse is
one, super toys are bent, then absolutely channel
situation, join us, now see
how you can do it, you
can also buy puck in the same way, so
what is morning topper, basically, super soft
edition, way, take more time, short term
plan because I use it, there is a
special favorable wicket, the village will
sink, but his body, that's why
I have
set alarms on it,
whether I call it certificate, friend, I am
looking at my profit, you can change my choice but to change
and the person suffering from it is vitamin  There are 135 these
poems which is very less so tears
can be taken on political leader and if you do
n't have time near Haldi Chowk then also
you can take it in advance, there is
no reaction, you can change your chart or vacation up
double water through
your health problems, if for some reason you are with another company, you
want to port your policy, that is, you
want to preserve from one company to another
without the same notification, maybe you are
leaving your policy to the party high command,
you want to keep quiet or you are also
feeling good,
you should use subscriber so that you are
not spoiled due to vacation,
so send a photo, pro-test
exam on one side from the telecom provider to the other
side, Airtel Pooja
and noise, then your number does not change there, so
my friend, if your number is less, it does
not get spoiled under Sirumalani portability, that you
get full till Ali, then you should remember the notification of Amazon,
not green chilli and its admin  About that
company G paper life process right now till last every
minute they are
saying that you have a
simple process that
everything is starting to
happen to you so this was nine wickets from friends
and how can you add notification about it
how can you forgive the
details effective it seemed like his
hands and his navel is that solarium rather in
front of us you can make the family happy, if you have any
question then you
can adopt any insignificant vacation
you can always ask in the comment section below
our WhatsApp number email id
is missions some reminder before going if
you have not subscribed to our channel yet
second strike is admitted in surgical strike
as I have got
this test done in my opinion Mithilesh Choudhary studio